# **GABRIEL AIZMAN**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ANALYST **REACT WEB DEVELOPER** 





## CONTACT





+54 9 1165858350



gabaiz88@gmail.com





https://mi-portfolio-gabaiz88.vercel.app



https://github.com/gabaiz88



# **LENGUAGES**



## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS

- GITHUB
- SQL
- C#
- CYPRESS.IO
- PHOTOSHOP
- SELENIUM IDE

#### **ABOUT**

For the last 2 years, I have been involved in programming languages such as JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS, SASS and C#. Prior to this, I worked in the banking and financial sector for over 14 years. These roles allowed me to develop leadership and management skills, as well as effective communication and collaboration skills. In the last year I studied and trained in the IT area, by taking Web Development courses, as well as undertaking the Systems Analyst career in ORT Institute in Buenos Aires. I'm looking for a new challenge that would allow me to further develop my system analyst skills.



### **EXPERIENCE**

#### BANCO CREDICOOP COOP, LTDO.

### -HEAD TELLER / BRANCH OPERATIONS **MANAGER**

Mar 2020 - Aug 2022

-TELLER

Jun 2014 - Mar 2020

#### **METROPOLIS CIA. FIANANCIERA**

-CREDIT RISK ANALYST

Dec 2012 - Jun 2014

-HEAD TELLER

May 2010 - Dec 2012



### **EDUCATION**

#### -INSTITUTO ORT ARGENTINA

Aug 2021 - Present

SYSTEMS ANALYST

-CODER HOUSE

Feb 2023 - Mar 2023

**REACT.JS** 

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

**JAVASCRIPT** 

Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

**-UDEMY** 

Feb 2023 - Mar 2023

**SOFTWARE TESTING**